Finding Aid for the Alfred H. Bartles Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- DETAILED CONTAINER LIST
  - Series D: Correspondence
    - Subseries 1: Non-Family and Professional
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional (Box 35)
        - Nordwall, Trugve, 1986, Apr.-1988; Related correspondence under Universal Edition (Box 35, Folder 19)
        - Noten Fuchs Antiquariat (Frankfurt-am-Main, Germany) (Box 35, Folder 20)
        - O’Neil, Gisela (Box 35, Folder 21)
        - O’Reilly, Sally (Baton Rouge, Louisiana?) (Box 35, Folder 22)
        - Ohio University (Box 35, Folder 23)
        - Opryland USA (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 35, Folder 24)
        - Ostoich, Mark and Lyn (Box 35, Folder 25)
        - Ottawa Philharmonic Orchestra (Ottawa, Ontario) (Box 35, Folder 26)
        - Owsley, Harriet, Undated, 1956, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 27)
        - Owsley, Harriet, 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 28)
        - Owsley, Harriet, 1982-1989 (Box 35, Folder 29)
        - Pädagogische Hochschule Esslingen, Undated, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 30)
        - Pädagogische Hochschule Esslingen, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 31)
        - Pädagogische Hochschule Esslingen, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 32)
        - Page, Willis and Jean (Box 35, Folder 33)
        - Parker, Charlotte (Box 35, Folder 34)
        - Parker, Craig B. (Los Angeles, California) (Box 35, Folder 35)
        - Payne, Basil, Undated, 1980-1982 (Box 35, Folder 36)
        - Payne, Basil, 1983-1987 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional (Box 36)
        - Pegram, Wayne (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Pensione Pitti Palace (Florence, Italy) (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - Pereira, Alexander von (Vienna, Austria) (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - Perera, Carolyn (Massachusetts) (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Peter, Christoph (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Petit, David (Germany) (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - Pfandler (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - Phillips, Harvey (Bloomington, Indiana) (Box 36, Folder 8)
        - Phillips, Phyllis and Les, Undated, 1979-1989 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - Phillips, Phyllis and Les, 1990-1996 (Box 36, Folder 10)
        - Phonograph Records Manufacturers (Box 36, Folder 11)
        - Piano-Fischer Musikhaus KG (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 36, Folder 12)
        - Pickle, Jerry T. (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 36, Folder 13)
        - Plath, Helmut and Ruth (Bönnigheim, Germany) (Box 36, Folder 14)
        - Pokorny, Gene (St. Louis, Missouri and Woods Cross, Utah) (Box 36, Folder 15)
        - Prager-Sayler, Madeline and Richard (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 36, Folder 16)
        - Pratt, Anne (Wilton, New Hampshire) (Box 36, Folder 17)
        - Preston, William Hall (Bill) (Booneville, Mississippi) (Box 36, Folder 18)
        - Prohaska, Miljenko (Zagreb, Yugoslavia) (Box 36, Folder 19)
        - Pusch, Ruth (Chestnut Ridge, New York) (Box 36, Folder 20)
        - Puschmann, Helga (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 36, Folder 21)
        - R., Véronique and Tom (Lyon, France) (Box 36, Folder 22)
        - Ramsay, Neal (Tennessee) (Box 36, Folder 23)
        - Rapp, Dorothea (Box 36, Folder 24)
        - Reid, Isaac (Mount Vernon, Iowa) (Box 36, Folder 25)
        - Reinhart, Carole D. (Vienna, Austria) (Box 36, Folder 26)
        - Reisebüro Wilcke (Box 36, Folder 27)
        - Reneau, Mark (Chattanooga, Tennessee) (Box 36, Folder 28)
        - Rettig, Denny, Richard, and Chara, Undated, 1959-1977 (Box 36, Folder 29)
        - Rettig, Denny, Richard, and Chara, 1978-1996 (Box 36, Folder 30)
        - Rilling, Helmut (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 36, Folder 31)
        - Robbins, Channing (New York, New York) (Box 36, Folder 32)
        - Röders, Gerd (Box 36, Folder 33)
        - Root, Johnny and Nancy (Jackson Heights, New York) (Box 36, Folder 34)
        - Rose, George (Box 36, Folder 35)
        - Rossé, F. Blanche (Redington Shores, Florida) (Box 36, Folder 36)
        - Roth, Richard (Box 36, Folder 37)
        - Rudiakov, Michael, Trudie, and Shoshana (Yonkers, New York) (Box 36, Folder 38)
        - Rudkin, Ron (Winston-Salem, North Carolina) (Box 36, Folder 39)
        - Rudolf Steiner Foundation, Inc. (New York, New York) (Box 36, Folder 40)
        - Rudolf Steiner Institute (Box 36, Folder 41)
        - Rudolf Steiner School (New York, New York) (Box 36, Folder 42)
        - Russell, Wilbur W. (Bill) (Hendersonville, North Carolina) (Box 36, Folder 43)
        - Ryman, Robert and Merrill (Box 36, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional (Box 37)
        - St. Goar, Maria (Chattanooga, Tennessee) (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - St. Louis Symphony Orchestra (St. Louis, Missouri) (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Salzer, Felix and Hedi, Undated, 1966-1986 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Salzer, Felix and Hedi, 1987-1992 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Sawyer, Cameron (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - Sawyer, John F. (Del) and Phyllis, Undated, 1960-1970 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - Sawyer, John F. (Del) and Phyllis, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - Sawyer, John F. (Del) and Phyllis, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - Sawyer, John F. (Del) and Patricia, 1981-1984 (Box 37, Folder 9)
        - Sawyer, John F. (Del) and Patricia, 1985-1991 (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - Schachter, Carl (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - Scherl & Roth, Inc. (Cleveland, Ohio) (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - Scherman, Thomas (New York, New York) (Box 37, Folder 13)
        - Schiller College, Undated, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - Schiller College, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 15)
        - Schiller College, 1973-1979 (Box 37, Folder 16)
        - Schmelz, Herbert and Eva Distler- (Fellbach, Germany) (Box 37, Folder 17)
        - Schmidt (Box 37, Folder 18)
        - Schmutterer, Gerhard and Marilyn (Sioux Falls, South Dakota) (Box 37, Folder 19)
        - Schneider (Box 37, Folder 20)
        - Schorr, Dieter (Box 37, Folder 21)
        - Schott Musik International (Mainz) (Box 37, Folder 22)
        - Schrade, Ewald (Box 37, Folder 23)
        - Schwarz, Gerard (Weehawken, New Jersey) (Box 37, Folder 24)
        - Schwink, Hazel (Box 37, Folder 25)
        - Shaw, David (Monsey, New York) (Box 37, Folder 26)
        - Silva, Luigi (Box 37, Folder 27)
        - Skaggs, Jerry (Box 37, Folder 28)
        - Sloan, David (Oxford, Mississippi) (Box 37, Folder 29)
        - Sloan, John (Box 37, Folder 30)
        - Society for Asian and Comparative Philosophy (Box 37, Folder 31)
        - Solow, Jeffrey (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania) (Box 37, Folder 32)
        - Sorenson, Trudi Szaroleta (Greenbrae, California) (Box 37, Folder 33)
        - Southern Colorado State College (Pueblo, Colorado) (Box 37, Folder 34)
        - Southern Illinois University (Carbondale, Illinois) (Box 37, Folder 35)
        - Spahr, Robert (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 37, Folder 36)
        - Späth, Fritz und Gisèle (Bönnigheim, Germany) (Box 37, Folder 37)
        - Spencer, Feli, Mrs. (Box 37, Folder 38)
        - Spiegel-Volkmann, [PMiria] (Box 37, Folder 39)
        - Spurbeck, Peter (Memphis, Tennessee) (Box 37, Folder 40)
        - Staar, René (Geneva, Switzerland) (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, Non-Family and Professional (Box 38)
        - Staatliche Hochschule für Musik Heidelberg-Mannheim (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Staatliche Hochschule für Musik Trossingen (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Staatliche Hochschule für Musik und Darstellende Kunst (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Starker, Janos (Bloomington, Indiana) (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Sterkel, Hilda (Heilbronn, Germany) (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Landeshauptstadt Stuttgart (Box 38, Folder 6)
          Chief correspondent: Gerhard Lang, Bürgermeister
        - Stuttgarter Musikschule (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Stuttgarter Nachrichten (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Süddeutscher Rundfunk Stuttgart (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Swift-Dorr Publications, Inc. (Oneonta, New York) (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - Symphony Society of San Antonio (San Antonio, Texas) (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Tardiff, Paul (Greenville, North Carolina) (Box 38, Folder 12)
        - Täte, Sarah (Tupelo, Mississippi) (Box 38, Folder 13)
        - Teal, Christian (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 38, Folder 14)
        - Tennessee Technological University, Undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
        - Tennessee Technological University, 1971-1973 (Box 38, Folder 16)
        - Tennessee Technological University, 1974-1981 (Box 38, Folder 17)
        - Tichman, Herbert (Box 38, Folder 18)
        - Toronto Symphony Orchestra Association (Toronto, Ontario) (Box 38, Folder 19)
        - The Travelers Companies (Hartford, Connecticut) (Box 38, Folder 20)
        - Tslaa, Norman and Kathy (Box 38, Folder 21)
        - Tuba Center Quality Brass (Eichenau bei München) (Box 38, Folder 22)
        - Ulrich, Reinhard (Box 38, Folder 23)
        - United States Navy, Public Affairs (Box 38, Folder 24)
          Chief correspondents: Lumpkin, Pickett
          Wiley
        - Universal Edition, Undated, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 25)
        - Universal Edition, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 26)
        - Universal Edition, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 27)
        - Universal Edition, 1991-1994 (Box 38, Folder 28)
        - Universal Edition, 1995-2004 (Box 38, Folder 29)
          Related correspondence under Füssl, Karl Heinz
          Related correspondence under Hanisch, Gucki
          Related correspondence under Norwall, Trygve
        - University of Maryland (College Park, Maryland) (Box 38, Folder 30)
        - University of North Carolina—Greensboro (Greensboro, N.C.) (Box 38, Folder 31)
        - University of the South (Box 38, Folder 32)
        - Valante, Harold (Westport, Connecticut) (Box 38, Folder 33)
        - Van Oordt, Peter and Kari, Undated, 1958-1968 (Box 38, Folder 34)
        - Van Oordt, Peter and Kari, 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 35)
        - Van Oordt, Peter and Kari, 1980-1983 (Box 38, Folder 36)
        - Van Oordt, Peter and Kari, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 37)
        - Van Oordt, Peter and Kari, 1987-1993 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional (Box 39)
        - Vancouver Symphony Society (Vancouver, B.C.) (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Vanilla Music Publications (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - Varga, Laszlo (San Francisco, California) (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Verein für ein Freies Schulwesen (Uhlandshöhe) (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Verein für Krebsforschung (Ariesheim, Switzerland) (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - Villringer, Gustel (Karlsruhe, Germany) (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Violoncello Society, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Voigt, Walter (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Volkswagen Versicherungsdienst GmbH (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Vryica, Peter (Graz, Austria) (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Waldorf Education in the West of the World (Sussex, England) (Box 39, Folder 11)
          Chief correspondent: Godwin, Manning
        - Wangenheim, Volker (Bad Godesberg) (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - Washington State University (Pullman, Washington) (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - Wattenbarger, James (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - Webb, Charles, Kenda, Mark (Bloomington, Indiana) (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - Weinstein, A. (Austria?) (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - Wendt, Charles (Iowa City, Iowa) (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - White, Helen (Box 39, Folder 18)
        - Whitney, Mark (Athens, Ohio and Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 39, Folder 19)
        - Wiemer, Matthias (Box 39, Folder 20)
        - Williams, Harold (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 39, Folder 21)
        - Wilson, Michael (Worcestershire, England) (Box 39, Folder 22)
        - Witt, Hilda (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 39, Folder 23)
        - Worgul, Helga (Heidelberg, Germany) (Box 39, Folder 24)
        - Wright, [?] (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 39, Folder 25)
        - Yilalys, Lisa Aldridge and Miguel (Box 39, Folder 26)
        - Zabach, Florian (Box 39, Folder 27)
        - Zemlinsky, Louise (New York, New York) (Box 39, Folder 28)
        - Zepernick, Werner (Box 39, Folder 29)
        - Zotos, Stefanos (Düsseldorf, Germany) (Box 39, Folder 30)
        - Unidentified, Undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
        - Unidentified, 1954-1968 (Box 39, Folder 32)
        - Unidentified, 1970-1974 (Box 39, Folder 33)
        - Unidentified, 1975-1977 (Box 39, Folder 34)
        - Unidentified, 1981-2000 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Series D: Correspondence
    - Subseries 2: Family
      - Correspondence—Family (Box 40)
        - Adams, Anita and Tom (Evanston, Illinois) (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - Adams, Howell and Madeline (Atlanta, Georgia) (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Almon, Clopper (Sr.) and Kats, Undated, 1963-1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - Almon, Clopper (Sr.) and Kats, 1974-1989 (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Almon, Clopper (Jr.) and Shirley, Undated, 1960-1970 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Almon, Clopper (Jr.) and Shirley, 1971-1975 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Almon, Clopper (Jr.) and Joan, Undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Almon, Clopper (Jr.) and Joan, 1976-1986 (Box 40, Folder 8)
        - Almon, Clopper (Jr.) and Joan, 1987-1991 (Box 40, Folder 9)
        - Almon, Clopper (Jr.) and Joan, 1992-1997, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - Bartles, Arloa (Tempe, Arizona) (Box 40, Folder 11)
        - Bartles, Isabel, Undated, 1979, Jan.-Sept. (Box 40, Folder 12)
        - Bartles, Isabel, 1979, Oct.-Dec. (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - Bartles, Isabel, 1980, Jan.-Feb. (Box 40, Folder 14)
        - Bartles, Isabel, 1980, Sept.-1981 (Box 40, Folder 15)
        - Bartles, Julia (Emahiser) (Box 40, Folder 16)
        - Bartles, Lois (Lee) (Box 40, Folder 17)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, Undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1939, 1953-1955 (Box 40, Folder 19)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 20)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1957, Jan.-Feb. (Box 40, Folder 21)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1957, Mar.-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence—Family (Box 41)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1957, May-Jun. (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1957, Jul.-Aug. (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1957, Sept.-Dec. (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1958, Jan.-Feb. (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1958, Mar.-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1958, May (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1958, Sept.-Dec. (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1959, Jan.-Feb. (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1959, Mar.-Jun. (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1959, Sept.-Dec. (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence—Family (Box 42)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1960, Jan.-Mar. (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1960, Apr.-May (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1960, Aug.-Nov. (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1961, Jan.-Apr. (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1961, May-Nov. (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1962, Mar.-Aug. (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1962, Sept.-Oct. (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1962, Nov.-Dec. (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1963, Jan.-Feb. (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1963, Mar.-May (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1963, Jun.-Sept. (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1963, Oct.-Nov. (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1963, Dec. (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence—Family (Box 43)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1964, Jan.-Feb. (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1964, Mar.-Apr. (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1964, Jul.-Oct. (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1964, Nov.-Dec. (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Outgoing, 1965-1968 (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, Undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1952-1957 (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1961, Jan.-Apr. (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1961, May-Oct. (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1961, Nov.-Dec. (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence—Family (Box 44)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1963, Jan.-Feb. (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1963, Mar.-May (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Incoming, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Bartles, Martha Howell—Condolences, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith—Undated, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith—1953, May-Jun. 9 (Box 44, Folder 6)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith—1953, Jun. 10-19 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1953, Jun. 20-30 (Box 44, Folder 8)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1953, Jul. (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1956-1958, Feb. 15 (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1958, Feb. 16-Mar. 10 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1958, Mar. 11-18 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1960-1961 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1968, 1978, Oct. (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - Bartles, Martha Smith, 1978, Nov., 1988 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence—Family (Box 45)
        - Chenoweth, Avery (Sr.) and Kitty (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - Chenoweth, Avery (Jr.) and Isabel (Box 45, Folder 2)
        - Dohrmann, Molly and Richard (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 45, Folder 3)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., Undated, 1956-1957 (Box 45, Folder 4)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1958-1960 (Box 45, Folder 5)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1961 (Box 45, Folder 6)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1962 (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1963 (Box 45, Folder 8)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1964, Jan.-Apr. (Box 45, Folder 9)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1964, May.-Sept. (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1965, Jan.-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 11)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1965, Sept-1968 (Box 45, Folder 12)
        - Ewing, Esmond, Frances, Robert (Bob), et al., 1969-1980 (Box 45, Folder 13)
          Includes legal documents
        - Frank, Arthur (Sr.), Jane, Arthur (Jr.), Harriet (Welsh), ‘Hayno’[?], Undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
        - Frank, Arthur (Sr.), Jane, Arthur (Jr.), Harriet (Welsh), ‘Hayno’[?], 1961-1963 (Box 45, Folder 15)
        - Frank, Arthur (Sr.), Jane, Arthur (Jr.), Harriet (Welsh), ‘Hayno’[?], 1964-1982 (Box 45, Folder 16)
        - Frank, Arthur (Sr.), Jane, Arthur (Jr.), Harriet (Welsh), ‘Hayno’[?], 1983-1989 (Box 45, Folder 17)
        - Hart, Dabney (Atlanta, Georgia), Undated, 1978-1984 (Box 45, Folder 18)
        - Hart, Dabney (Atlanta, Georgia), 1986-1994 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence—Family (Box 46)
        - Howell, Isabel—Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1954-1959 (Box 46, Folder 2)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1961-1966 (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1967-1970, Jun. (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1970, Jul.-Dec. (Box 46, Folder 5)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 6)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1972, Jan.-Jul. (Box 46, Folder 7)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1972, Aug.-Dec. (Box 46, Folder 8)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1973, Jan.-Feb. (Box 46, Folder 9)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1973, Mar.-Apr. (Box 46, Folder 10)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1973, Jun.-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 11)
        - Howell, Isabel, 1974-1978 (Box 46, Folder 12)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Sr.) and Marie, Undated, 1942-1960 (Box 46, Folder 13)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Sr.), 1961-1963 (Box 46, Folder 14)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, Undated, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 15)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 16)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 17)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1973, 1976-1977, Sept. (Box 46, Folder 18)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1977, Oct.-Dec. (Box 46, Folder 19)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1978, Jan.-Jun. (Box 46, Folder 20)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1978, Jul.-Dec. (Box 46, Folder 21)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 22)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 23)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 24)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence—Family (Box 47)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Howell, Morton B. (Jr.) and Nancy, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 12)
          This series includes documents related to Nanhaven, the Howell Family Cottage located in Beersheba Springs, Tennessee
        - Howell, Samuel H. and Virginia, Undated, 1963-1979 (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - Howell, Samuel H. and Virginia, 1981-1991 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - Howell, William W. (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - Johnson, Lewis and Hattie (Pittsfield, Massachusetts) (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Smith, Nellie and Family, Undated, 195-?-1968 (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - Smith, Nellie and Family, 1970-1978 (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Smith, Nellie and Family, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - Smith, Nellie and Family, 1981-1984 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Series E: Miscellaneous Materials
    - Miscellaneous—Personal (Box 48)
      - Documents/Contracts, Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 1)
        Note: Many contracts and other records (especially if used in applications) may be held within correspondence (Series D).
        Various ID and membership cards
        Mantovani Tour Orchestra contract, 1958
        Charter of the Howell Cottage [Nanhaven, Beersheba Springs, Tennessee]
        Rice Datsun Security Agreement and Disclosure Statement, 1976
        Trust Agreement between Al Laney (Albert Gillis Laney) and the Colonial Bank and Trust Company and Alfred H. Bartles, Trustees, 1976